question_data =[ {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment Film","question":"The Xenomorph from the science fiction film Alien has acidic ood.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"Entertainment: Music","question":"Pete Townshends solo album, White City: A Novel, is set in the metropolitan area of Chicago.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Animals","question":"You can tell the age of a ladybird by counting the spots on his back.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"There are 86400 seconds in a day.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Music","question":"Ashley Frangipane performs under the stage name Halsey.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga","question":"In Chobits, Hideki found Chii in his apartment.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Music","question":"Rapper Snoop Doggs real name is Cordozar Calvin Broadus, Jr.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Pluto is a planet.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Stagecoach owned South West Trains before losing the rights to FirstGroup and MTR in March of 2017.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"In Pokmon Sun and Moon, a male Salandit can evolve to a Salazzle.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Television","question":"AMCs The Walking Dead, Rick, Carl, Daryl, Morgan, Carol and Maggie were introduced to us in Season 1.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"In Half-Life 2, if you play the zombies speech in reverse, they actually speak coherent English.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"Hidden in the files for Mario Kart Arcade GP is a picture of the Beslan school hostage crisis.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Music","question":"Metallica collaborated with Rowan Atkinsons Mr Bean on a 1992 comic relief single.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Musicals &amp; Theatres","question":"IMAX stands for Image Maximum.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"In Undertale, having a Fun Value set to 56-57 will play the Wrong Number Song Call.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Typewriter is the longest word that can be typed using only the first row on a QWERTY keyboard.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"The game Jetpack Joyride was created by Redbrick Studios.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Film","question":"Ewan McGregor did not know the name of the second prequel film of Star Wars during and after filming.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Science: Computers","question":"All program codes have to be compiled into an executable file in order to be run. This file can then be executed on any machine.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]}]
